

About Me

I'm quick learner and would to get experiences working with IT group and try to solve problems with my skills. Can afford for new experiences and learn other techinques strongly and the best.



09 7766 76924



kaungkhantzaw.mml223@gmail.com



North Dagon, Yangon

LANGUAGE

- English (Pre-Intermediate)
- Myanmar

EXPERTISE

- Java SE
- MySQL Database
- HTML, CSS, Javascript
- Bootstrap
- PHP. Laravel Framwork

KAUNG KHANT ZAW

Junior Web Developer

EXPERIENCE

University Projects 2017-2019

Mini Projects such as Automatic Hand-Wash and Fishy Drying Machine

StudyRightNow School's Projects 2021-2023

Java Standard Edition Project

(Library Management System)

Database Designing Project

(Library Management System,

Bus Ticket Booking System,

Jewelry Website Shop System)

PHP Project

Jewelry Website Shop System

EDUCATION

Technology University (Dawei)

4th yr Electronic Commucation 2016-2020

StudyRightNow Technology School (Mandalay)

Java, Database & Web Development Courses 2021-2023

SKILLS SUMMARY

Web Design 76%

Web Development 81 %

Database Management 70%

Dasktop Application 60%